evolvhealth.com 2011-03-20

# Evolv | Privacy Policy

## INFORMATION COLLECTION

EvolvHealth, LLC (referred to herein as "EvolvHealth", "our", "us" or "we") is the sole owner of the information collected on our websites and on the replicated EvolvHealth websites that we provide for use by independent contractor Members (hereafter the "websites"). We collect information from Independent Members ("Members"), customers and visitors to the websites at different points on the websites.

### Personally Identifiable Information

Through your use of or visits to our websites, you may be required or requested to provide personally identifiable information to us. Personally identifiable information is any piece of information which can potentially be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person including names, addresses, email addresses, telephone numbers, social security and tax identification numbers, and credit card information.

### Member and Customer Registration

In order to become a Member, an applicant must provide biographical and contact information (such as name, mailing address, telephone numbers, and email address) to us. We also require an applicant's Social Security Number or Federal Tax ID Number so that we may prepare and file necessary non-employee compensation forms for the IRS. Certain customers may be required to register in order to purchase products directly from us ("Registered Customers"). Registered Customers will be required to provide contact information (such as name, mailing address, telephone number(s), and email address) and payment information (such as credit card or checking account information). We use this information to maintain contact with Members and Registered Customers, and to process Member and Registered Customer orders.

### Downline Genealogy Reports

As a network marketing company, EvolvHealth provides certain information to Members regarding the other Members and Registered Customers enrolled in a Member's downline marketing organization. If you enroll as a Member or Registered Customer with EvolvHealth, your name, email address, and telephone number will be provided to your Sponsor and the Member immediately above your Sponsor. No other personally identifiable information will be shared with other Members. Such information is made available to EvolvHealth Members subject to a confidentiality and non-disclosure covenant in the agreement that each Member enters into with EvolvHealth.

### Product or Service Purchases

When a customer, Registered Customer, or Member purchases products or services from us through any of our websites, the purchaser must provide us with mailing and contact information as well as payment information. This information is used for billing and payment purposes and to fill orders.

## INFORMATION USE

### Personally Identifiable Information

Personally identifiable information that is collected from customers, Members and Registered Customers through Member and Customer Registration, Product or Services Purchases and/or Surveys is used as described above. EvolvHealth DOES NOT share personally identifiable information except as may be necessary to process and fill an order. EvolvHealth may share aggregated information from time to time with its partners, vendors or other third parties. When such aggregate information is shared by EvolvHealth, no personally identifiable information is shared.

### Profile Information

EvolvHealth stores information that it collects through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of visitors to our websites ("users"), including customers, Registered Customers, and Members. A profile is stored information that EvolvHealth keeps on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Profile information is tied to the user's personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. EvolvHealth does not share profile information with other third parties.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on the websites. EvolvHealth uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

By setting a cookie on a user's computer, users do not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while at the websites. If a user rejects the cookie, the user will still be able to use the site. The only drawback to this is that the user may need to enter his or her password every time he or she accesses the site.

### Log Files

Like most standard website servers EvolvHealth's websites use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our web-based service. We use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

### Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

EvolvHealth employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help EvolvHealth to better manage content on the websites by informing it what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are not tied to users' personally identifiable information.

In addition, EvolvHealth uses clear gifs in its HTML-based emails to let it know which emails have been opened by the recipients. This allows EvolvHealth to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

## COMMUNICATIONS FROM US

### Special Offers and Updates

EvolvHealth sends all new Members and Registered Customers a welcoming email to verify password, username, and acceptance of the Member Agreement or Customer Agreement. All Members and Registered Customers will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Customers who have not registered with EvolvHealth and who grant permission will also receive occasional information on products, services, special deals, and the like.

### Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send Members and/or customers an email. Generally, Members may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

### Member and Customer Service

EvolvHealth communicates with Members and Registered Customers via email, regular mail and telephone on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regard to issues relating to their EvolvHealth business. EvolvHealth communicates with other customers with respect to products or services purchased by such customers from EvolvHealth. Such communications may be by email, regular mail or telephone.

## SHARING

### Legal Disclaimer

Though EvolvHealth makes every effort to preserve user privacy, EvolvHealth may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on EvolvHealth.

### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

EvolvHealth shares aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

### These are the instances in which we will share users' personal information:

EvolvHealth DOES NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information about users with any Third Parties.

### Third Party Fulfillment

EvolvHealth uses an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill Members for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

### Service Providers

EvolvHealth partners with other third parties to provide specific services. When necessary to provide services or products to Members, Registered Customers, and other customers, we share names and/or other contact information with service providers and vendors. Such third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

### Business Transitions

In the event EvolvHealth goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, the personal information of Members and customers will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. If as a result of the business transition, a Member's or customer's personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, the Member or customer will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

### Choice

Users are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

### Links

EvolvHealth's websites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that EvolvHealth is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by EvolvHealth websites.

### Security

EvolvHealth takes every precaution to protect all users' information. When users submit sensitive information via EvolvHealth's websites, their information is protected both online and offline.

When the Member Application, Customer Registration, and/or online order forms ask users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as the Member Application and Agreement and online order forms, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'.

While EvolvHealth uses SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, the Company also does everything in our power to protect user information offline. All user information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in EvolvHealth's offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. ALL employees are kept up-to-date on Company security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment.

## MISCELLANEOUS

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

EvolvHealth reserves the right to amend or change this Privacy Policy at any time at its sole discretion. It is your responsibility to periodically access this Privacy Policy by clicking on the Privacy Policy link at our home page.

### Making Changes to Your Personally Identifiable Information

Members and Registered Customers may update your personal information as necessary by logging into eCenter, the back office website, or contacting our member services department which allows them to access and edit their registration account information. In addition, you may contact us at [info@evolvhealth.com](mailto:info@evolvhealth.com) to update your profile.

### Protecting Children

EvolvHealth is committed to the safety of our children. Persons under the age of 18 may not enroll as EvolvHealth Members or register as customers. Children under the age of 13 may not purchase products through any of our websites. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from such children at this site or any of its other sites.

### Questions

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to [privacypolicy@evolvhealth.com](mailto:privacypolicy@evolvhealth.com), or by mail to EvolvHealth, Galleria Tower 2, 23rd Floor, 13455 Noel Road, Dallas, Texas 75240.

### Effective Date

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is October 1, 2009.

© 2020 EvolvHealth, LLC. All Rights Reserved.

You will need to have the free Adobe® Reader® to open the PDF file.  
Click the link to download the latest version.
